有一条灰色的走廊 但然后...
There was this gray hall, but then...
一切都白得刺眼
everything was, like, so white.
我们有进展了
We're making progress.
不只是在一张桌子上醒来
It's not just waking up on a table.
现在还有与人的互动
It's human interaction.
但那感觉不像“人” 更像噩梦
This didn't feel human, this felt like a nightmare.
她为什么连续说一串事实
I mean, why is she rattling off a bunch of facts?
他们对她做了什么
What are they doing to her?
我只知道她是关键人员
All I know is she's essential.
她甚至没有认出我
She didn't even recognize me.
你所认识的珍玛仍在那里
The Gemma you know is still in there.
等你救她出来后 就是你们两人一起在这个世界里了
And when you get her out, it will be the two of you out here together.
讨价还价
Bargaining.
你知道那是什么吧
You know what that is?
什么意思
What do you mean?
是其中一个阶段
Well, it's one of the stages.
你会思考各种你愿意去做的事
You think about all the things you'd do,
各种你可以改变的地方 只为了让那个人回来
and all the ways you'd change to get that person back.
你会减少饮酒 愿意多去倾听
You'd drink less. You'd listen more.
虽然很蠢 但你还是会去做
It's dumb, but you do it anyway.
这很正常
It's normal.
是
Yeah.
但对我来说 也许那人真的会回来
But for me, it might actually happen.
是一幅画 上面有一条黑色走廊
It was a sketch of a black hallway,
还有一部黑色的电梯 只往下走
with a black elevator that only goes down.
所以我们下面有一层
So there's a floor beneath us.
一定是他们关她的地方
That must be where they're keeping her.
后面有指示
There were directions on the back.
让我们看看
Well, let's see it.
我没拿 把它放在海报后面了
I left it there, behind the poster.
你为什么不直接拿走
Why didn't you just take it?
反正我没拿 好吗
I just didn't, okay?
我现在不想惹麻烦
I don't wanna get in trouble right now.
好吧 我才不在乎 我去拿吧
Okay. Well, I don't give a shit about that, so I'll go get it.
你是说它在展现 你“英勇”的那幅海报后面
You said it's behind the poster of you actually being brave?
对 去你的 你们不是无所不知
Okay, yeah. Fuck you. You don't know everything.
那就告诉我们啊
Then tell us.
没关系的
It's okay.
好的 我还有通行证 所以我可以现在去休息室
Okay. Well, I still have a hall pass, so I can go to the break room now,
- 然后我们午餐后动手 - 是 也许吧
- and then we can start after lunch. - Yeah. Maybe.
也许
Maybe?
今早你们出电梯时 是把蛋蛋也割了 这么没种
Did everyone sever their balls in the elevator this morning?
我饿死了
I'm starving.
马克
Mark?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
人生切割术
第二季 第六集
先生
Sir?
请坐
Have a seat.
我昨天进行了表现评核
I had my performance review yesterday.
结果如何
How did it go?
提出了许多合理的问题 我期待能尽快解决
Many valid concerns were raised, which I look forward to addressing.
我为你开心
I'm glad for you.
我感觉应该提醒你
I feel I should remind you,
你从这个奖学金项目毕业的前提
you cannot graduate from this fellowship
是我评定你具备参与冬潮的资格
until I have deemed you Wintertide material.
也就是说 你要善用时间 专注于本职
This will mean using your time well, focusing on your own duties,
根除你幼稚无知的本质
and eradicating from your essence childish folly.
我理解 先生
I understand, sir.
今天余下时间 我会忙于工作
I shall be busy for the rest of the day.
我相信你会代我管理好分离楼层
I trust you can steward the floor in my stead?
- 当然 - 很好
- Of course. - Good.
你可以回到日常工位了
You may sit at your regular desk.
谢谢你 米尔奇克先生
Thank you, Mr. Milchick.
(该进行表现评核了 塞斯米尔奇克)
- 他威胁你  - 在我离开时
- He threatened you? - As I was leaving.
在电梯里
In the elevator.
他们想恐吓我们
They're trying to intimidate us.
- 分裂我们 - 而且...
- Divide us. - And also--
这样我们就不会合作
It's so that we won't work together,
因为他们知道我们合作的后果 我要去拿那张地图
because they know what will happen if we do. I'm gonna go get that map.
赫莉 我们同床了
Helly, we shared vessels.
什么
What's that?
我们...
Well, we...
我们曾发生关系
we had sex.
好吧
Okay.
你和...你是说 你们在健康咨询时做的
You and... Like, in a Wellness session?
不 不是...凯西女士
No. Not... Ms. Casey.
是在团建的时候
It was at the retreat.
在你的帐篷里
In your tent.
对
Yeah.
你是说...
You mean...
显然 你知道 我以为那是你
I mean, obviously, you know, I thought it was you.
因为我一直对你有感觉
'Cause, you know, I've been having those feelings since,
在紧急加班前就有了
like, before the OTC.
所以当她...我就...我并不知道 好吗
So when she... I just... I had no idea, okay?
- 嗯哼 - 我很抱歉 赫莉
- Uh-huh. - I'm sorry, Helly.
我...她蒙骗了我
I... She tricked me.
我是说 我...的确是想的 但她...
I mean, I... you know, wanted to, but she...
她蒙骗了我们两人
she tricked both of us.
估计又是她的一个策略
It's probably another tactic.
用来离间我们的感情
Something to drive a wedge between us.
- 像是... - 赫莉
- Like-- - Helly--
我去散散步
I'm gonna go for a walk.
赫莉 对不起 我以为是你
Helly, I'm sorry. I thought it was you.
但那不是我
But it wasn't me.
是 我去走走
Yeah, I'm just gonna go walk around.
第一次约会 我猜猜
First date, let me guess.
- 水肺潜水 - 泰国餐
- Scuba. - Thai food.
不错
Nice.
不过你去年的确上过水肺潜水课
Though you did take scuba lessons last year.
是吗 哪片海
Yeah? Which sea?
是在游泳池
It was in a pool.
好吧 酷
Okay. Cool.
挺贵的
It was a little expensive.
你尝试过许多不同的爱好
You've had a lot of phases.
水肺潜水 木工
Scuba diving, woodworking.
哇 所以我外面的自己生活很丰富
Wow. So, my outie's really diverse.
自酿啤酒
Garage beer-making.
也许我是想在地上的世界 找到自己杰出的领域 像地下的自己一样
Maybe I'm trying to find something I excel in up there, like I do down here.
有时我好奇 是不是纯粹因为你不快乐
I sometimes wonder if you're just not happy.
我想一定不是因为那个
I'm sure it's not that.
因为你知道... 在这里和你见面时 我超级快乐
'Cause, like, you know... I mean, here, with you, I'm super happy.
我想听你讲我子女的各种故事
I just, like, wanna hear about all my offspring
还有盯着你的脸看
and stare at your face.
- 抱歉 有点奇怪 - 不会
- Sorry. That was weird. - No.
你这么说很贴心
It was really sweet.
我喜欢
I like it.
我喜欢这样见面
I like this.
我希望我们真的能在一起
I wish we could really be together.
一直在一起
Like, all the time.
我们是一直在一起呀
I mean, we are.
不是吗
Aren't we?
你和他是的
You and him are.
但和我不是
But I'm not.
再试着抱一抱 可以吗
Is it okay if we try the hug again?
我挺喜欢拥抱的部分
I kind of like the hugging.
噢 嘿 我正要来找你呢
Oh, hey. I was coming to find you.
我也在找你
Same.
听着 我真的很抱歉
Look, I am so sorry.
我都无法想象那是什么感觉...
I can't even imagine what it must be like to--
你以为她是我
You thought it was me.
百分之百
Hundred percent.
也就是说你想要
Which means you wanted to.
和我一起
With me.
对
Yeah.
让我不爽的是她得到了 但我没有
What sucks is that she got to have that, and I didn't.
她利用我来骗我的朋友
That she used me to trick my friends.
用我的身体去接近你
Used my body to get close to you.
她每天早上给我穿衣服 仿佛我是个婴儿
That she dresses me in the morning like I'm a baby.
她控制着我 这家公司和所有人
That she controls me, and this company, and all of us.
令人作呕
It's disgusting.
嘿 你要不要我具体说说发生了什么
Hey, do you want me to, like, describe what happened?
我觉得你有权知道
Like, I feel like you have every right to know.
不 我不想要她的记忆
No. I don't want her memory.
好的
Okay.
我想要自己的记忆
I want my own.
你想吗
Would you like that?
是的 我想
Yeah, I'd like that.
但要怎么做到
But how?
帐篷
A tent.
我好紧张
I'm nervous.
我也是
Me too.
- 你也是 - 没事的
- You too. - It's okay.
好
Okay.
等等
Wait.
可以吗
Yes?
是
Yes.
(过多使用大词 问题)
你必须根除你幼稚无知的本质
You must eradicate from your essence childish folly.
你必须根除自己的幼稚无知
You must eradicate from yourself childish folly.
你必须摆脱稚气
You must abandon childish things.
你必须长大
You must grow up.
长大
Grow up.
成长
Grow.
和我的这次有不同吗
Was it different with me?
噢 不好 你流血了
Oh, no, you're bleeding.
不 是你在流血
No, you are.
还有两分钟
You have two minutes left.
分离楼层的湿度维持在45%不变
Humidity on the severed floor is maintained at a consistent 45%.
一定是其他原因
It must be something else.
你打了他吗
Did you punch him?
今天没有
I mean, not today.
开始流鼻血时 你们在做什么
What were you doing when the nosebleed occurred?
我们正在精检文件
We were refining something.
你有鼻中隔偏曲吗
Do you have a deviated septum?
我不知道那是什么
Well, I don't know what that is.
需要我给你的鼻孔里抹凡士林吗
Would you like me to put petroleum jelly in your nostrils?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
还有其他症状吗
Any other symptoms?
有先兆头痛或幻觉吗
Any auras or hallucinations?
没有 血好像止住了 我感觉好些了
No. I think it stopped. I feel better.
我要为你测血压
I'm going to take your blood pressure.
(卢蒙认证)
你在哪
Where are you?
我在卢蒙
I'm at Lumon.
- 什么  - 什么
- What? - What?
- 该死的 我刚... - 马克
- Fuck. I was just-- - Mark?
你...
Wha--
你刚才在卢蒙
Were you just at Lumon?
现在几点
What time is it?
你是在卢蒙 还是在你的地下室 和我一起
Are you at Lumon or in your basement with me?
我不知道
I don't know.
你记得有个走廊吗
Do you remember a hallway?
黑色的走廊
A black hallway?
我记得...好吧
I remember... Okay.
我记得有张桌子
I remember a desk.
我记得...糟糕
I remember... Shit.
又是一个交叉记忆
That was another crossover memory.
是近期的 这是好事
A recent one. That's good.
你会感觉有些时间段缺失了 但最后都会记起来的
You'll feel gaps in time until it all comes back together.
“最后”是什么时候
Well, when the fuck is that gonna happen?
我们必须加强效果 加快进程
We need to enhance. Speed up the process.
这样安全吗
Is that safe?
有小概率会出血
There's a slight chance of hemorrhage.
好吧 所以我会流血致死
Okay. So, me bleeding to death.
未必
Not necessarily.
我们把芯片淹没
We'll flood the chip itself.
把芯片淹没
Flood the chip?
- 透过你脑中的洞 - 老天爷
- Through the hole in your head. - Jesus Christ.
- 那个洞本已存在 - 好吧...
- That you've already got. - Okay--
你知道吗
You know what?
你还是别碰我
Get the fuck off me.
- 我不干了 - 我们很接近了 会成功的
- I am not doing this, okay? - We're close. It's happening.
- 给我拆了 现在 拜托 - 我们必须推进
- Get this shit off right now! Please. - We need to push!
拆了...
Get it off--
天 我...好饿
God. I'm fu... I'm starving.
那也是恢复记忆引起的
That's also from reintegration.
好吧 这样
Okay, you know what?
我去吃饭
I'm gonna go eat.
该死的
Fuck.
你好
Hello.
你是什么人
Who the hell are you?
开个玩笑
It's a joke.
- 进来吧 嗨 - 好的
- Come on in. Hey. - Okay.
搞什么
What the heck?
菲尔德斯正在烹饪火腿
Fields is tending the ham.
希望你喜欢孜然汁
I hope you like a cumin glaze.
是 喜欢
Yes, of course.
- 你不喜欢吗  - 我喜欢
- Do you not? - No, I do.
阿提拉
Attila.
是 阿提拉
Yes, Attila?
你刚是问酱汁吗
Did you just ask about the glaze?
- 是的 - 别问
- I did. - Well, don't.
我已经淋上了
I've already put it on.
我刚想说 我们也有玉米
I was gonna say we also have corn.
噢 是
Oh, yes.
我们可以给他吃一堆玉米粒
We could feed him a pile of loose corn.
我真搞不懂你公司里的自己
What your innie ever saw in this Philistine
看上这大老粗的哪一点
is beyond me.
我猜你是菲尔德斯
Fields, I presume.
是的
Yes.
- 欧文 - 欧文
- Irving. - Irving.
是
Yes.
欢迎回到我们家
Welcome back to our home.
是 上次的事 我很抱歉
Yes. I'm sorry about the last time.
你们一定感觉隐私被侵犯了
I'm sure that felt quite invasive.
才不会
Nonsense.
我的就是你的
What's mine's yours.
你还带了酒
And you've brought wine.
欧文 你去公司的路上 从没有人朝你泼血吗
Irving, no one's ever thrown blood on you on your way into work?
- 没有 - 不是血 是颜料
- No. - It wasn't blood. It was paint.
那也是为了引起血战
Meant to evoke blood.
你当时不是这么说的
Not what you said.
我的意思是 健康大脑那帮人都是疯子
The Whole Mind people are off the deep end, is my point.
伯特 你去公司工作的原因是什么
And, Burt, how did you come to be at the company?
- 我  - 是 我很好奇
- Me? - Yes, I'm very curious.
事实上 是耶稣指引我步入卢蒙的大门
Well, as a matter of fact, I was guided to Lumon's door by Jesus.
耶稣基督
Jesus Christ?
正是他
That's the one.
你应该就此打住 让他猜 你到底是什么意思
You should just leave it at that, and let him wonder what the hell you meant.
不 我们加入路德教会已经好些年了
No, we'd been attending the Lutheran church for some years.
另外提一下 在我年轻时 我可以说是
And I should mention that I'd been what you might call a scoundrel
一个人渣
in my younger days.
这么说已经算客气了
To put it mildly.
有个周日 吃早餐时 菲尔德斯直接问我
So, one Sunday at breakfast, Fields asked me point blank,
我觉得自己会上天堂吗
do I think I'm going to heaven?
早餐的常见话题
As one asks at breakfast.
我假装思考了一下 但我知道答案是不会
I pretend to think about it, but I know the answer is no.
对此我的回应是“那我自己在上面 待到永恒 怎么消磨时光 ”
To which I replied, "What am I supposed to do up there for eternity all by myself?"
- 了解 - 所以我们搭火车去教堂
- I see. - So we hop on the train to church,
那天的布道主题恰恰是分离...
and it so happens the sermon that day is about severance...
- 是 - 当时还是个新概念
- Yeah. - ...which was still very new at the time.
牧师说...
And the pastor says--
仿佛他听过我们的谈话一样
As if he'd been listening to our conversation,
他说教会的立场是 公司里的自己是
he said the church's stance is that innies are, you know,
完整的个人 拥有灵魂
complete individuals, with souls...
在审判时与外面的自己是分开的
that can be judged separately from their outie.
所以 公司里的自己可以上天堂
So, an innie can go to heaven.
外面的自己下地狱
Whilst the outie burns.
我发誓 我们不是宗教狂热分子
We're not zealots, I swear.
但我们觉得 如果这是真的
But we figured that if it were true,
也许伯特的一部分能通过这个方式...
it may be a way for part of Burt to--
你知道的
You know...
天
Wow.
- 他在想离席的借口了 - 不 只是...
- He's looking for the exit. - No, it's just--
所以我们希望伯特公司里的自己上天堂
So, the hope was for Burt's innie to go to heaven.
对 与我一起
Yes. With me.
格雷琴 到月底了
Gretch, it's the end of the month.
那些销售员只想达到业绩目标 把车卖出去
Those salesmen are just dying to hit their numbers and get cars off the lot.
所以价格非常优惠
They'll basically be giving me money.
好吧
Okay. Fine.
只是试驾
Just test drive only.
我不会真买
I won't commit to anything.
- 谢谢 - 不
- Thank you. - No.
你没告诉我发生了什么 你又去卢蒙了 对吗
You didn't tell me how'd it go. You went back to Lumon, right?
不
No.
感觉怎样
That good?
他们取消了
They canceled it.
我没见到他...你
I didn't see him... you.
- 吃光啦 - 吃光啦
- Happy plate. - Happy plate.
去和妹妹玩吧
Go play with your sister.
取消了 怎么回事
Canceled it? What happened?
他们没说 可能你太忙了
They didn't say. Guess you got too busy.
- 嘿 伙计 尝尝 不要 好吧 - 不
- Hey. Buddy. Try it. No. Okay. - No.
谢谢
Thank you.
马克斯科特
Mark Scout.
我就说像你 我是海伦娜伊根 我在卢蒙工作
Thought that was you. I'm Helena Eagan. I work at Lumon.
是 不 我知道你是谁
Yeah. No, I know who you are.
正式见到你很高兴
Well, it's nice to officially meet you.
你吃饱了吗
Have you had enough to eat?
是 挺饱的
Yeah, quite possibly.
希望公司也有给你好吃好喝
I hope they're feeding you at work.
可以坐下吗
May I?
请
Please.
遇到你真好
It's really great to run into you.
对了 关于你的工作 我听到的都是赞美之词
I've heard nothing but good things about your work, by the way.
谢谢 关于我的工作 我一个词都没听过
Thank you. I've heard nothing at all about my work, so...
分离幽默 真风趣
Severance humor. That's so clever.
陈述事实而已
And so easy.
听着 对那天晚上的系统错误 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry for the systemic error from the other night.
系统错误
The systemic error?
你是说加班那事
You mean the overtime thing?
对 紧急加班
Yes. The OTC.
那件事根本不该发生的 而且以后绝不会发生
It never should have happened, and it never will again.
我们知道那决不能反映 本公司的实质 我们一定会改善
We take pride as a company to be better than that, and we will be better.
- 很高兴听到你这么说 谢谢 - 不用客气
- Well, that's nice to hear. Thanks. - Of course.
所以你对一切都知情
So, you know all about it then.
是 我对一切都知情
Yes, I know all about it.
我是公司的老大 马克
I'm, like, the head of the company, Mark.
是哦 好蠢 抱歉
Right. Dumb. Sorry.
是 你应该感到抱歉
Yeah, you should be sorry.
- 真的吗 好吧 - 开玩笑的
- Really? Okay. - I'm kidding.
你显然不蠢
You're clearly not dumb.
不知道 你...
I don't know. You...
你发明了革命性的医学手术
You're the one who invented a revolutionary medical procedure.
嘿 那可不是我发明的
Hey, now, that was not me.
是我父亲
That was my father.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
有空的话 你应该见见他
You should meet him sometime.
你父亲
Your father?
对啊 有何不可
Sure. Why not?
你这就想带我回家见家长了
You wanna take me home to Dad already?
是 我觉得是时候了
Yeah, I think it's finally time.
好吧 行 见就见
Okay. Sure. Let's do it.
你是第一个我带回去的
You'd be the first.
- 所以不用有压力 - 对 完全不用
- So, no pressure. - Yeah. None whatsoever.
不过 说句正经的 有时间 我很想听听你的经历
But seriously, I'd love to hear about your experiences sometime.
是 好
Okay. Yeah.
关于分离吗
About severance?
我是说加班...那天晚上
I meant the overtime con... I meant the other night.
我无法想象那有多令人疑惑
I mean, I can't imagine how confusing that must have been.
甚至是创伤性的
Traumatic, even.
我知道你已经经历了许多 失去你的妻子等等
And I know you've already been through so much with losing your wife and all.
汉娜
Hanna.
珍玛
Gemma.
对 珍玛 抱歉
Right. Gemma. Sorry.
是车祸 对吗
It was a car accident, right?
是的
That's right.
是 太唏嘘了
Yeah, such a shame.
她还那么年轻
She was so young.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我没事 快吃完了
I'm fine. I'm just about finished here.
好的 是
Okay. Right.
很高兴见到你 海伦娜
Well, it was nice to meet you, Helena.
是 彼此彼此 马克
Yeah. You too, Mark.
怎么了
What is it?
没什么
Nothing.
晚安
Good night.
(嬉笑)
(基尔 地区道路地图)
(分离员工名单)
(道格科曼 车祸 2007年5月)
(和解协议是分离的原因吗 )
(卡萝迪雷 她结婚了吗 )
(伯特古德曼 基尔 格尔海滨路3329号)
我们过去会叫彼此“宝贝”
We used to call each other hon,
大概十年前变成了“阿提拉”
then about ten years ago that became Attila.
因为...你熟悉历史吗
Because... Do you know history?
- 是 - 他熟悉历史
- Yeah. - He knows history.
不是十年前 是20年前
And it wasn't ten years ago. It was 20.
- 不对 - 就是
- No. - Yes!
因为我记得当时 我们在和你的卢蒙伴侣喝酒
Because I remember we were having drinks with your Lumon partner.
吓了他一跳
Quite startled him.
第一个分离办事处 不是在12年前创建的吗
Didn't the first severed office open 12 years ago?
- 是的 - 对
- Yes, it did. - Yeah.
喝得差不多了吧
Maybe that's enough of that.
其实这玉米很特别
You know the corn is very special.
你觉得你们俩在公司发生过关系吗
Do you think you two ever made love at work?
菲尔德斯 老天
Fields, Jesus.
我们不能成熟点 就事论事吗
Can we not just be pragmatic adults about this?
你们俩不做保护措施发生关系 并非完全不可能
There is a nonzero chance that the two of you had unprotected sex.
因此 我觉得有权这么问
And so, I felt the right to ask.
你还要继续羞辱我们的客人吗
Are you done humiliating our guest?
你可能觉得我疯了 但我没有
Sounds like I'm mad, but I'm not.
我们把话摊开了说吧
Cards on the table.
我和盖尔牧师谈过这件事
I've been talking to Pastor Gale about this,
我认为公司里的自己有权体验爱
and I believe that innies deserve to experience love.
我是认真的
I mean it.
我希望那份爱很美
And I hope it was beautiful.
抱歉我表现得那么混账
Sorry for being a dick.
我们做吧
Let's do it.
今晚就做
Tonight.
(超声波)
好了
There.
要等多久
How long will it take?
很快的
It'll be fast.
很快 多快
Fast. How fast?
我好紧张
I'm nervous.
是
Yes.
搞什么
What the fuck?
别乱动
Don't move like that.
你必须保持头部静止
You have to keep your head still.
别管它
Ignore it.
告诉我...
Tell me--
马克
Mark?
我的车在车道上 她知道我在
My car's in the driveway. She knows I'm here.
不
No...
- 马克 - 是
- Mark. - Yeah?
嘿
Hey.
哥们 我给你留了五条留言 你感觉好些了吗
Dude, I left you, like, five messages. Are you better?
不 我还病着
No, I'm still sick.
我们在进行企业间谍行动期间 你别不接电话啊
Well, you can't not pick up when we're doing corporate espionage shit.
泛光灯那招完全失败了 对吗
The floodlight thing was a bust, right?
因为我有个点子 要稍微更蠢一点
Because I have had an idea that is a little dumber.
好吧 德文
Okay, Devon...
你记得婴儿营的那个富太吗
Do you remember the rich lady from baby camp?
有点把我扳弯的那个
The one I, like, kind of had a crush on?
- 我在想... - 对 听我说
- I was thinking-- - Yeah. Look,
我已经在尝试另一个办法了
I'm already trying something else.
好吧 什么办法
Okay. What are you trying?
你不用操心了
Just don't worry about it.
- 这话什么意思  - 我自己来
- What the fuck does that mean? - I'm doing it myself.
得了吧
Fuck that.
你为什么要把我排除在外
Why are you trying to cut me out of this?
该死
Shit.
我没有 德文
I'm really not, Devon.
- 你就在这么做啊 - 好吧
- You literally are. - Okay, fine.
是 但我本来就没让你帮忙
I am, but I didn't ask for your help!
我正式表示:去你的
Fuck you, officially.
那股味道是什么
And what is that smell?
什么味道
What smell?
天啊
Oh, my God.
马克
Mark.
别碰他
Don't touch him.
你是谁啊
Who the fuck are you?
马克
Mark?
没事 伙计 没事的
It's okay, buddy. It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
谢谢你们招待的火腿
Thank you for the spare ham.
菲尔德斯...
Is Fields...
他没事的 明天起来他就会觉得丢脸了
He's fine. He'll be embarrassed tomorrow.
你知道 他有些事记不太准
You know, he gets fuzzy.
比如说我20年前在卢蒙工作
Like saying I worked at Lumon 20 years ago,
那时当然还不存在分离
which is, of course, before severance even existed.
当然
Of course.
- 抱歉 - 不 今晚很开心
- Sorry. - No, this was fun.
- 是吗  - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
我们应该找时间再聚
So, we should do it again sometime.
你 我和菲尔德斯 还是只有你我
You, me, Fields? Or you, me?
不 我是说菲尔德斯也一起
No, I meant with Fields.
- 对 - 是吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
对 但 都可以
Yeah. But, you know, it's either way.
好
Good.
- 晚安 伯特 - 晚安
- Good night, Burt. - Good night.